{
    "subject": "resource/Isaac_Gr\u00fcnewald",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Expressionism",
    "human_readable": "Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was associated with Expressionism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8980638384819031,
            "question": "How did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald's work reflect the themes of Expressionism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621442317962646,
            "question": "What impact did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald have on the Expressionist movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8197042346000671,
            "question": "What art movement was Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872100830078125,
            "question": "What type of art was Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6425139904022217,
            "question": "To which artistic style did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6173641681671143,
            "question": "Who were some other prominent artists associated with Expressionism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5270453095436096,
            "question": "In what artistic period did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48688557744026184,
            "question": "Name an art movement that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is known for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4617420434951782,
            "question": "Describe the characteristics of the art movement Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11224116384983063,
            "question": "What are some key features of Expressionist art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was associated with Expressionism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8158_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the characteristics of the art movement Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald was part of.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8158_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an art movement that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is known for.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8158_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what artistic period did Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8158_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8158_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is an artist from the Expressionist Art art movement (59.txt), that he had a leading position in the Swedish modernist movement and became its representative in Sweden's contemporary art debate, which was associated with Expressionism (40.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Isaac Gr\u00fcnewald is an artist from the Expressionist Art art movement and refers to him as an expressionist, which supports the statement that he was associated with Expressionism."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}